historycollection.co 2016-10-24

# Privacy Policy - History Collection

Privacy Policy

Historycollection.co’s Privacy Policy

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor and used to notify consumers about updates to our Web.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by contacting us at the contact us link below.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

E-Mail Policy

Historycollection.co does not sell, rent, exchange or otherwise disclosed personal e mail information collected on this site. Personal information is collected only with your permission.
